Guide to the John E. Brennan Outdoor Advertising Survey Reports, 1947-1980 and undated RL.00148
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Outdoor Advertising Survey Reports, 1947-1980 (bulk 1947-1960s)
  - Reports Organized by City (alphabetical)
    - Cincinnati #83, 1955 July (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati #84, 1955 Aug. (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati #85, 1955 Sept. (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati #86, 1955 Oct. (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati #87, 1955 Nov. (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati #88, 1955 Dec. (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati #89, 1956 Jan. (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati #90, 1956 Feb. (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati #91, 1956 Mar. (Box 10)
    - Cincinnati #92, 1956 Apr. (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #93, 1956 May (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #94, 1956 June (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #95, 1956 July (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #96, 1956 Aug. (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #97, 1956 Sept. (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #98, 1956 Oct. (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #99, 1956 Nov. (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #100, 1956 Dec. (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #101, 1957 Jan. (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #102, 1957 Feb. (Box 11)
    - Cincinnati #103, 1957 Mar. (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #104, 1957 Apr. (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #105, 1957 May (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #106, 1957 June (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #107, 1957 July (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #108, 1957 Aug. (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #109, 1957 Sept. (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #110, 1957 Oct. (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #111, 1957 Nov. (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #112, 1957 Dec. (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #113, 1958 Jan. (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #114, 1958 Feb. (Box 12)
    - Cincinnati #115, 1958 Mar. (Box 13)
    - Cincinnati #116, 1958 Apr. (Box 13)
    - Cincinnati #117, 1958 May (Box 13)
    - Cincinnati #118, 1958 June (Box 13)
    - Cincinnati #119, 1958 July (Box 13)
    - Cleveland #1, 1965 Nov. (Box 13)
    - Columbus, Ga. #1, 1963 July (Box 13)
    - Columbus, Ga. #2, 1964 Jan. (Box 13)
    - Dallas #1, 1949 May (Box 13)
    - Dallas #2, 1949 June (Box 13)
    - Dallas #3, 1949 July (Box 13)
    - Dallas #4, 1949 Aug. (Box 13)
    - Dallas #5, 1949 Sept. (Box 13)
    - Dallas #6, 1949 Oct. (Box 13)
    - Dallas #7, 1949 Nov. (Box 14)
    - Dallas #8, 1949 Dec. (Box 14)
    - Dallas #9, 1950 Jan. (Box 14)
    - Dallas #10, 1950 Feb. (Box 14)
    - Dallas #11, 1950 Mar. (Box 14)
    - Dallas #12, 1950 Apr. (Box 14)
    - Dallas #13, 1950 May (Box 14)
    - Dallas #14, 1950 June (Box 14)
    - Dallas #15, 1950 July (Box 14)
    - Dallas #16, 1950 Aug. (Box 14)
    - Dallas #17, 1950 Sept. (Box 14)
    - Dallas #18, 1950 Oct. (Box 14)
    - Dallas #19, 1950 Nov. (Box 15)
    - Dallas #20, 1950 Dec. (Box 15)
    - Dallas #21, 1951 Jan. (Box 15)
    - Dallas #22, 1951 Feb. (Box 15)
    - Dallas #23, 1951 Mar. (Box 15)
    - Dallas #24, 1951 Apr. (Box 15)
    - Dallas #25, 1951 May (Box 15)
    - Dallas #26, 1951 June (Box 15)
    - Dallas #27, 1951 July (Box 15)
    - Dallas #28, 1951 Aug. (Box 15)
    - Dallas #29, 1951 Sept. (Box 15)
    - Dallas #30, 1951 Oct. (Box 15)
    - Dallas #31, 1951 Nov. (Box 15)
    - Dallas #32, 1951 Dec. (Box 16)
    - Dallas #33, 1952 Jan. (Box 16)
    - Dallas #34, 1952 Feb. (Box 16)
    - Dallas #35, 1952 Mar. (Box 16)
    - Dallas #36, 1952 Apr. (Box 16)
    - Dallas #37, 1952 May (Box 16)
    - Dallas #38, 1952 June (Box 16)
    - Dallas #39, 1952 July (Box 16)
    - Dallas #40, 1952 Aug. (Box 16)
    - Dallas #41, 1952 Oct. 1 (Box 16)
    - Dallas #42, 1952 Oct. 28 (Box 16)
    - Dallas #43, 1952 Nov. (Box 16)
    - Dallas #44, 1952 Dec. (Box 16)
    - Dallas #45, 1953 Jan. (Box 16)
    - Dallas #46, 1953 Feb. (Box 17)
    - Dallas #47, 1953 Mar. (Box 17)
    - Dallas #48, 1953 Apr. (Box 17)
    - Dallas #49, 1953 May (Box 17)
    - Dallas #50, 1953 June (Box 17)
    - Dallas #51, 1953 July (Box 17)
    - Dallas #52, 1953 Aug. (Box 17)
    - Dallas #53, 1953 Sept. (Box 17)
    - Dallas #54, 1953 Oct. (Box 17)
    - Dallas #55, 1953 Nov. (Box 17)
    - Dallas #56, 1953 Dec. (Box 17)
    - Dallas #57, 1954 Jan. (Box 17)
    - Dallas #58, 1954 Mar. 1 (Box 18)
    - Dallas #59, 1954 Mar. 29 (Box 18)
    - Dallas #60, 1954 Apr. (Box 18)
    - Dallas #61, 1954 May (Box 18)
    - Dallas #62, 1954 June (Box 18)
    - Dallas #63, 1954 July (Box 18)
    - Dallas #64, 1954 Aug. (Box 18)
    - Dallas #65, 1954 Sept. (Box 18)
    - Dallas #66, 1954 Oct. (Box 18)
    - Dallas #67, 1954 Nov. (Box 18)
    - Dallas #68, 1954 Dec. (Box 18)
    - Dallas #69, 1955 Jan. (Box 18)
    - Dallas #70, 1955 Feb. (Box 19)
    - Dallas #71, 1955 Mar. (Box 19)
    - Dallas #72, 1955 Apr. (Box 19)
    - Dallas #73, 1955 May (Box 19)
    - Dallas #74, 1955 June (Box 19)
    - Dallas #75, 1955 July (Box 19)
    - Dallas #76, 1955 Aug., 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Denver #1, 1963 Sept. (Box 19)
    - Denver #2, 1963 Oct. (Box 19)
    - Des Moines #1, 1963 Oct. (Box 19)
    - Detroit #1, 1963 July (Box 20)
    - Detroit #2, 1963 Aug. (Box 20)
    - Detroit #3, 1963 Oct. (Box 20)
    - Detroit #4, 1963 Dec. (Box 20)
    - Detroit #5, 1964 Feb. (Box 20)
    - Detroit #6, 1964 Apr. (Box 20)
    - Detroit #7, 1966 Apr. (Box 20)
    - Detroit #8, 1966 June (Box 20)
    - Fresno #1, 1948 Dec. (Box 20)
    - Fresno #2, 1949 Feb. (Box 20)
    - Fresno #3, 1949 Mar. 1 (Box 20)
    - Fresno #4, 1949 Mar. 29 (Box 20)
    - Fresno #1, 1963 Aug. (Box 20)
    - Houston #1, 1955 Sept. (Box 21)
    - Houston #2, 1955 Oct. (Box 21)
    - Houston #3, 1955 Nov. (Box 21)
    - Houston #4, 1955 Dec. (Box 21)
    - Houston #5, 1956 Jan. (Box 21)
    - Houston #6, 1956 Feb. (Box 21)
    - Houston #7, 1956 Mar. (Box 21)
    - Houston #8, 1956 Apr. (Box 21)
    - Houston #9, 1956 May (Box 21)
    - Houston #10, 1956 June (Box 21)
    - Houston #11, 1956 July (Box 21)
    - Houston #12, 1956 Aug. (Box 22)
    - Houston #13, 1956 Sept. (Box 22)
    - Houston #14, 1956 Oct. (Box 22)
    - Houston #15, 1956 Nov. (Box 22)
    - Houston #16, 1956 Dec. (Box 22)
    - Houston #17, 1957 Jan. (Box 22)
    - Houston #18, 1957 Feb. (Box 22)
    - Houston #19, 1957 Mar. (Box 22)
    - Houston #20, 1957 Apr. (Box 22)
    - Houston #21, 1957 May (Box 22)
    - Houston #22, 1957 June (Box 23)
    - Houston #23, 1957 July (Box 23)
    - Houston #24, 1957 Aug. (Box 23)
    - Houston #25, 1957 Sept. (Box 23)
    - Houston #26, 1957 Oct. (Box 23)
    - Houston #27, 1957 Nov. (Box 23)
    - Houston #28, 1957 Dec. (Box 23)
    - Houston #29, 1958 Jan. (Box 23)
    - Houston #30, 1958 Feb. (Box 23)
    - Houston #31, 1958 Mar. (Box 23)
    - Houston #32, 1958 Apr. (Box 23)
    - Houston #33, 1958 May (Box 23)
    - Houston #34, 1958 June (Box 24)
    - Houston #35, 1958 July (Box 24)
    - Houston #36, 1958 Aug. (Box 24)
    - Houston #37, 1958 Sept. (Box 24)
    - Houston #38, 1958 Oct. (Box 24)
    - Houston #39, 1958 Nov. (Box 24)
    - Houston #40, 1958 Dec. (Box 24)
    - Houston #41, 1959 Jan. (Box 24)
    - Houston #42, 1959 Mar. 2 (Box 24)
    - Houston #43, 1959 Mar. 25 (Box 24)
    - Houston #44, 1959 Apr. (Box 24)
    - Houston #45, 1959 May (Box 24)
    - Houston #46, 1959 June (Box 24)
    - Houston #47, 1959 July (Box 24)
    - Houston #48, 1959 Aug. (Box 25)
    - Houston #49, 1959 Sept. (Box 25)
    - Houston #50, 1959 Oct. (Box 25)
    - Houston #51, 1959 Nov. (Box 25)
    - Houston #52, 1959 Dec. (Box 25)
    - Houston #53, 1960 Jan. (Box 25)
    - Houston #54, 1960 Feb. (Box 25)
    - Houston #55, 1960 Mar. (Box 25)
    - Houston #56, 1960 Apr. (Box 25)
    - Houston #57, 1960 May (Box 25)
    - Houston #58, 1960 June (Box 25)
    - Houston #59, 1960 July (Box 25)
    - Houston #60, 1960 Aug., 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Houston #61, 1960 Sept. (Box 26)
    - Houston #62, 1960 Oct. (Box 26)
    - Houston #63, 1960 Nov. (Box 26)
    - Houston #64, 1960 Dec. (Box 26)
    - Houston #65, 1961 Jan. (Box 26)
    - Houston #66, 1961 Feb. (Box 26)
    - Houston #67, 1961 Mar. (Box 26)
    - Houston #68, 1961 Apr. (Box 26)
    - Houston #69, 1961 May (Box 26)
    - Houston #70, 1961 June (Box 26)
    - Houston #71, 1961 July (Box 26)
    - Houston #72, 1961 Aug. (Box 26)
    - Houston #73, 1961 Sept. (Box 26)
    - Houston #74, 1961 Oct. (Box 27)
    - Houston #75, 1961 Nov. (Box 27)
    - Houston #76, 1961 Dec. (Box 27)
    - Houston #77, 1962 Feb. (Box 27)
    - Houston #78, 1962 Mar. (Box 27)
    - Houston #79, 1962 Apr. (Box 27)
    - Houston #80, 1962 May (Box 27)
    - Houston #81, 1962 June (Box 27)
    - Houston #82, 1962 July (Box 27)
    - Houston #83, 1962 Aug. (Box 27)
    - Houston #84, 1962 Sept. (Box 27)
    - Houston #85, 1962 Oct. (Box 27)
    - Houston #86, 1962 Nov. (Box 28)
    - Houston #87, 1963 June (Box 28)
    - Houston #88, 1963 Oct. (Box 28)
    - Houston #89, 1963 Nov. (Box 28)
    - Houston #90, 1964 Feb. (Box 28)
    - Houston #91, 1964 June (Box 28)
    - Houston #92, 1964 July (Box 28)
    - Houston #93, 1964 Oct. (Box 28)
    - Houston #94, 1965 Jan. (Box 28)
    - Houston #95, 1965 Feb. (Box 28)
    - Houston #96, 1965 Mar. (Box 28)
    - Houston #97, 1965 May 10 (Box 28)
    - Houston #98, 1965 May 30 (Box 28)
    - Houston #99, 1965 June (Box 29)
    - Houston #100, 1965 July (Box 29)
    - Houston #101, 1966 Feb. (Box 29)
    - Houston #102, 1966 June (Box 29)
    - Houston #103, 1966 Aug. (Box 29)
    - Houston #104, 1966 Sept. (Box 29)
    - Indianapolis #1, 1963 Sept. (Box 29)
    - Indianapolis #2, 1963 Dec. (Box 29)
    - Jackson, Miss. #1 1964 Apr. (Box 29)
    - Jacksonville, Fla. #1, 1964 Apr. (Box 29)
    - Lima, Ohio #1, 1963 Oct. (Box 29)
    - Los Angeles #1, 1949 Apr. (Box 29)
    - Los Angeles #2, 1949 May (Box 29)
    - Los Angeles #3, 1949 June (Box 29)
    - Los Angeles #4, 1949 July (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #5, 1949 Aug. (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #6, 1949 Sept. (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #7, 1949 Oct. (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #8, 1949 Nov. (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #9, 1949 Dec. (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #10, 1950 Jan. (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #11, 1950 Feb. (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #12, 1950 Mar. (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #13, 1950 Apr. (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #14, 1950 May (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #15, 1950 June (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #16, 1950 July (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles #17, 1950 Aug. (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #18, 1950 Sept. (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #19, 1950 Oct. (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #20, 1950 Nov. (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #21, 1950 Dec. (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #22, 1951 Jan. (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #23, 1951 Feb. (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #24, 1951 Mar. (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #25, 1951 Apr. (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #26, 1951 May (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #27, 1951 June (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #28, 1951 July (Box 31)
    - Los Angeles #29, 1951 Aug. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #30, 1951 Sept. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #31, 1951 Oct. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #32, 1951 Nov. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #33, 1951 Dec. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #34, 1952 Jan. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #35, 1952 Feb. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #36, 1952 Mar. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #37, 1952 Apr. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #38, 1952 May (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #39, 1952 June (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #40, 1952 July (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #41, 1952 Aug. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #42, 1952 Sept. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #43, 1952 Oct. (Box 32)
    - Los Angeles #44, 1952 Nov. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #45, 1952 Dec. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #46, 1953 Jan. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #47, 1953 Feb. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #48, 1953 Mar. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #49, 1953 Apr. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #50, 1953 May (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #51, 1953 June (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #52, 1953 July (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #53, 1953 Aug. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #54, 1953 Sept. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #55, 1953 Oct. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #56, 1953 Nov. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #57, 1953 Dec. (Box 33)
    - Los Angeles #58, 1954 Jan. (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #59, 1954 Mar. 1 (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #60, 1954 Mar. 29 (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #61, 1954 Apr. (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #62, 1954 May (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #63, 1954 June (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #64, 1954 July (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #65, 1954 Aug. (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #66, 1954 Sept. (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #67, 1954 Oct. (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #68, 1954 Nov. (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #69, 1954 Dec. (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #70, 1955 Jan. (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #71, 1955 Feb. (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #72, 1955 Mar. (Box 34)
    - Los Angeles #73, 1955 Apr. (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #74, 1955 May (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #75, 1955 June (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #76, 1955 July (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #77, 1955 Aug. (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #78, 1955 Sept. (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #79, 1955 Oct. (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #80, 1955 Nov. (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #81, 1955 Dec. (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #82, 1956 Jan. (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #83, 1956 Feb. (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #84, 1956 Mar. (Box 35)
    - Los Angeles #85, 1956 Apr. (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #86, 1956 May (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #87, 1956 June (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #88, 1956 July (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #89, 1956 Aug. (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #90, 1956 Sept. (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #91, 1956 Oct. (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #92, 1956 Nov. (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #93, 1956 Dec. (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #94, 1957 Jan. (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #95, 1957 Feb. (Box 36)
    - Los Angeles #96, 1957 Mar. (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #97, 1957 Apr. (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #98, 1957 May (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #99, 1957 June (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #100, 1957 July (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #101, 1957 Aug. (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #102, 1957 Sept. (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #103, 1957 Oct. (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #104, 1957 Nov. (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #105, 1957 Dec. (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #106, 1958 Feb. (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #107, 1958 Mar. 1 (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #108, 1958 Mar. 29 (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #109, 1958 Apr. (Box 37)
    - Los Angeles #110, 1958 May (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #111, 1958 June (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #112, 1958 Aug. 2 (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #113, 1958 Aug. 30 (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #114, 1958 Sept. (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #115, 1958 Nov. 1 (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #116, 1958 Nov. 29 (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #117, 1958 Dec. (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #118, 1959 Jan. (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #119, 1959 Feb. (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #120, 1959 Mar., 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #121, 1959 Apr. (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #122, 1959 May (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #123, 1959 June (Box 38)
    - Los Angeles #124, 1959 July (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #125, 1959 Aug. (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #126, 1959 Oct. 1 (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #127, 1959 Oct. 28 (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #128, 1959 Nov. (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #129, 1959 Dec. (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #130, 1960 Jan. (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #131, 1960 Feb. (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #132, 1960 Mar. (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #133, 1960 Apr. (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #134, 1960 May (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #135, 1960 June (Box 39)
    - Los Angeles #136, 1960 July (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #137, 1960 Aug. (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #138, 1960 Sept. (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #139, 1960 Oct. (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #140, 1960 Nov. (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #141, 1960 Dec. (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #142, 1961 Jan. (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #143, 1961 Feb. (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #144, 1961 Mar. (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #145, 1961 Apr. (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #146, 1961 May (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #147, 1961 June (Box 40)
    - Los Angeles #148, 1961 July (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #149, 1961 Aug. (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #150, 1961 Sept. (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #151, 1961 Oct. (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #152, 1961 Nov. (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #153, 1961 Dec. (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #154, 1962 Jan. (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #155, 1962 Feb. (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #156, 1962 Mar. (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #157, 1962 Apr. (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #158, 1962 May (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #159, 1962 June (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #160, 1962 July (Box 41)
    - Los Angeles #161, 1962 Aug. (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #162, 1962 Sept. (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #163, 1962 Oct. (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #164, 1962 Nov. (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #165, 1962 Dec. (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #166, 1963 Jan. (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #167, 1963 Feb. (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #169, 1963 Apr. (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #170, 1963 May (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #171, 1963 June (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #172, 1963 July (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #173, 1963 Aug. (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #174, 1963 Sept. (Box 42)
    - Los Angeles #175, 1963 Oct. (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #176, 1963 Nov. (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #177, 1963 Dec. (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #178, 1964 Jan. (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #179, 1964 Feb. (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #180, 1964 Mar. (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #181, 1964 Apr. (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #182, 1964 May (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #183, 1964 June (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #184, 1964 July (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #185, 1964 Aug. (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #186, 1964 Sept. (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #187, 1964 Oct. (1 of 2) (Box 43)
    - Los Angeles #187, 1964 Oct. (2 of 2) (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #188, 1964 Nov. (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #189, 1964 Dec. (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #190, 1965 Jan. (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #191, 1965 Feb. (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #192, 1965 Mar. (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #193, 1965 Apr. 30 (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #194, 1965 Apr. 30 (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #195, 1965 May (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #196, 1965 June (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #197, 1965 July 30 (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #198, 1965 July 30 (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #199, 1965 Aug. (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #200, 1965 Sept. 30 (Box 44)
    - Los Angeles #201, 1965 Sept. 30 (Box 45)
    - Los Angeles #201, 1965 Sept. 30 (survey of children) (Box 45)
    - Los Angeles #202, 1965 Oct. (Box 45)
    - Los Angeles #203, 1965 Nov. (Box 45)
    - Los Angeles #204, 1965 Dec. (Box 45)
    - Los Angeles #205, 1966 Jan. (Box 45)
    - Los Angeles #206, 1966 Feb. (Box 45)
    - Los Angeles #207, 1966 Mar. (Box 45)
    - Los Angeles #208, 1966 Apr. (Box 45)
    - Los Angeles #209, 1966 May (Box 45)
    - Lubbock, Tex. #1, 1963 Oct. (Box 45)
    - Market Four Metro #1, 1963 June (Box 45)
    - Market Four Metro #2, 1963 Aug. (Box 45)
    - Market Four Metro #3, 1963 Oct. (Box 45)
    - Market Four Metro #4, 1963 Dec. (Box 46)
    - Market Four Metro #5, 1964 Feb. (Box 46)
    - Memphis #1, 1963 July (Box 46)
    - Memphis #2, 1963 Nov. (Box 46)
    - Memphis #3, 1964 May (Box 46)
    - Miami #1, 1963 May (Box 46)
    - Miami #2, 1963 Sept. (Box 46)
    - Miami #3, 1964 Jan. (Box 46)
    - Minneapolis #1, 1963 June (Box 46)
    - Minneapolis #2, 1963 Sept. (Box 46)
    - Minneapolis #3, 1963 Dec. (Box 46)
    - Minneapolis #4, 1964 Mar. (Box 46)
    - Montgomery, Ala. #1, 1963 Sept. (Box 46)
    - Montgomery, Ala. #2, 1964 Mar. (Box 46)
    - New Haven, Conn. #1, 1947 Oct. (Box 46)
    - New Haven, Conn. #2, 1947 Nov. (Box 46)
    - New Haven, Conn. #3, 1947 Dec. (Box 46)
    - New Haven, Conn. #4, 1948 Jan. (Box 46)
    - New Haven, Conn. #5, 1948 Feb. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #6, 1948 Mar. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #7, 1948 Apr. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #8, 1948 June (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #9, 1948 July (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #10, 1948 Aug. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #11, 1948 Sept. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #12, 1948 Oct. 1 (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #13, 1948 Oct. 28 (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #14, 1948 Nov. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #15, 1948 Dec. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #16, 1949 Feb. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #17, 1951 Oct. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #18, 1952 Jan. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #19, 1952 Feb. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #20, 1952 Mar. (Box 47)
    - New Haven, Conn. #21, 1952 Apr. (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #22, 1952 May (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #23, 1952 June (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #24, 1952 July (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #25, 1952 Aug. (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #26, 1952 Sept. (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #27, 1952 Oct. (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #28, 1952 Nov. (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #29, 1952 Dec. (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #30, 1953 Jan. (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #31, 1953 Feb. (Box 48)
    - New Haven, Conn. #32, 1953 Mar. (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #33, 1953 Apr. (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #34, 1953 May (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #35, 1953 June (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #36, 1953 July (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #37, 1953 Aug. (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #38, 1953 Sept. (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #39, 1953 Oct. (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #40, 1953 Nov. (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #41, 1953 Dec. (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #42, 1954 Jan. (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #43, 1954 Feb. (Box 49)
    - New Haven, Conn. #44, 1954 Mar. (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #45, 1954 Apr. (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #46, 1954 May (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #47, 1954 June (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #48, 1954 July (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #49, 1954 Aug. (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #50, 1954 Sept. (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #51, 1954 Oct. (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #52, 1954 Nov. (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #53, 1954 Dec. (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #54, 1955 Jan. (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #55, 1955 Feb. (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #56, 1955 Mar. (Box 50)
    - New Haven, Conn. #57, 1955 Apr. (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #58, 1955 May (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #59, 1955 June (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #60, 1955 July (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #61, 1955 Aug. (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #62, 1955 Sept. (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #63, 1955 Oct. (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #64, 1955 Nov. (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #65, 1955 Dec. (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #66, 1956 Jan. (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #67, 1956 Feb. (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #68, 1956 Mar. (Box 51)
    - New Haven, Conn. #69, 1956 Apr. (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #70, 1956 May (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #71, 1956 June (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #72, 1956 July (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #73, 1956 Aug. (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #74, 1956 Sept. (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #75, 1956 Oct. (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #76, 1956 Nov. (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #77, 1956 Dec. (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #78, 1957 Jan. (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #79, 1957 Feb. (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #80, 1957 Mar. (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #81, 1957 Apr. (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #82, 1957 May (Box 52)
    - New Haven, Conn. #83, 1957 June (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #84, 1957 July (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #85, 1957 Aug. (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #86, 1957 Sept. (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #87, 1957 Oct. (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #88, 1957 Nov. (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #89, 1957? Dec. (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #90, 1958 Jan. (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #91, 1958 Feb. (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #92, 1958 Mar. (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #93, 1958 Apr. (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #94, 1958 May (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #95, 1958 June (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn. #96, 1958 July (Box 53)
    - New Haven, Conn., #97, 1958 Aug. (Box 54)
    - New Haven, Conn., #98, 1958 Sept. (Box 54)
    - New Haven, Conn., #99, 1958 Oct. (Box 54)
    - New Haven, Conn., #100, 1958 Nov. (Box 54)